Guide to the Elliott School of International Affairs records, 1907-2005 RG0015
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Elliott School of International Affairs records
1907-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Elliott School of International Affairs. Office of the Dean
RG0015
13.25 Linear Feet
Collection includes publications, videocassettes, annual reports, by-laws, reports, meeting minutes, and appointment books. The material covers the dates 1907-2005. Subjects coverd in the collection include Egyptian project, inauguration activities, Soviet File Festival, publications, three La Rochell video cassettes, administrative files, conferences, faculty reports and meetings, graduate assistants, committee records, work study
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Elliott School of International Affairs.
Historical or Biographical Note
For more than a century, George Washington University has offered students an unbroken succession of international affairs programs. The institutional forerunners of the Elliott School began with the School of Comparative Jurisprudence and Diplomacy which, though it lasted only seven years (1898-1905), was followed by:
The School of Politics and Diplomacy, 1905-07; The College of the Political Sciences, 1907-13; The Department of International Law and Diplomacy (within Columbian College), 1913-28; The School of Government, 1928-60; The School of Government, Business, and International Affairs, 1960-66; The School of Public and International Affairs, 1966-87; and The School of International Affairs, 1987-88. The Elliott School of International Affairs, founded in 1988.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include publications, videocassettes, annual reports, by-laws, reports, meeting minutes, and appointment books. The material covers the dates 1907-2005. Subjects coverd in the collection include Egyptian project, inauguration activities, Soviet File Festival, publications, three La Rochell video cassettes, administrative files, conferences, faculty reports and meetings, graduate assistants, committee records, work study programs, dean's appointment books (1964-1993), Naval War College thesis.
Collection Organization
Organized into four series: Records, Publications and two series titled School files.
By-laws; Reports and studies; Washington (D.C.); Conferences; Reports and dissertations; Elliott School of International Affairs; George Washington University
- Records, 1907-1987; RG0015 Series 1; 1 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes announcements, brochures, flyers, programs, envelopes, applications, memorandums, bylaws, student handbooks, a directory, newsletters, speeches, stationary, certificate, and press releases. They range in date from 1907 to 1987. The materials concern the College of Political Sciences's courses, programs, faculty, lectures, and history; the School of Public and International Affairs (SPIA); the Foreign Affairs Intern Program; the Latin American Studies Program; Helen and Sergius Yakobson Graduate scholarship; international students; conferences; faculty; the National War Colleges; and SPIA's 1987 reorganization, calendar of events, programs, and lectures; "Public administration 1939-59-79"; the School of Government, Business, and International Affairs's Air Force advanced management program, accounting program, and other programs.
  - School of Comparative Jurisprudence and Diplomacy, 1898-2005 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Alumni Association - Elliott School of International Affairs, 1985-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association - School of Public and International Affairs Alumni Associations, 1971-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Comparative Jurisprudence and Diplomacy, School of (1898-1905), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Comparative Jurisprudence and Diplomacy, School of - Course on Finance, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Comparative Jursiprudence and Diplomacy, School of - Notes on the history and development of program, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Comparative Jurisprudence and Diplomacy, School of - Syllabus of the Outlines of Political History,1899 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Elliott School of International Affairs, 1991-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Elliott School of International Affairs - Brochures, 1988-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Elliott School of International Affairs - Graduate Programs, 1988-2000 ca. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Elliott School of International Affairs - History, 1987-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Elliott School of International Affairs - Publications, 1989-2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Elliott School of International Affairs - Publications - "Divided Diplomacy and the Next Administration", 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Association, 1907-1987 (Box 2)
  - Government, Business, and International Affairs, School of (1960-1966), 1961-10/17/1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Government, Business, and International Affairs, School of (1960-1966) - Air Force Advanced Management Program, 12/1955-7/31/1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Government, Business, and International Affairs, School of (1960-1966) - Programs, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Latin American Studies, 1965-10/27/1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Political Sciences, College of the, 6/1907-1909 ca. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of, 1969-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of - Calendars, 4/1/1986-10/5/1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of - Faculty - By Laws, 1976-1985, 4/2/1976-12/13/1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of - Graduate Programs, 1969-8 /1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of - Graduate Student Handbook, 8/1979-6/1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of - Programs at the War Colleges, 2/1962-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of - Reorganization, 1987, 1/20/1987-2/6/1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of (1966-1988) - Science, Technology, and Public Policy, 9/1970-4/1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Public and International Affairs, School of - Theses (M.A.I.A. degree), 1961-1965, 1961-4 /25/1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Public and International Affairs (School of) - Workshops, Seminars, Institutes, Conferences, Etc., 10/14/1986-10/15/1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Publications, 2000-2005; RG0015 Series 2; .25 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series contains the publications produced by the Elliott School of International Affairs entitled "The Briefing". They range in date from 2000-2005. A new issue comes out once a semester.
  - Briefing newsletter, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    General note
    This folder contains the Elliott School of International Affair's, "Briefing" newsletter. They range in date from Fall 2000- Spring 2001.
  - Briefing newsletter, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    This folder contains the Elliott School of International Affair's, "Briefing" newsletter. They range in date from Fall 2001- Spring 2002.
  - Briefing newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    This folder contains the Elliott School of International Affair's, "Briefing" newsletter. They range in date from Fall 2002- Spring 2003.
  - Briefing newsletter, 2002-2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    This folder contains the Elliott School of International Affair's "Briefing" newsletter. They range in date from Fall 2003- Spring 2005.
- School files, 1987-1990; RG0015 Series 3; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains calendars, Egyptian project, inauguration activities, soviet film festival, publications, three La Rochelle video cassettes. The material dates from 1987-90. There is material related to study abroad and the Global Information Revolution program.
  - School files, undated (Box 1)
  - Egyptian project, 03/1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Global Information Revolution Program, 10/1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Goheen, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Inauguration activities, 02/1989-04/1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Japan campuses proposals, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dean Ludlow study abroad, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - SIA Calendar, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Film Festival, Anna Lawton, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Film, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Publications, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - La Rochelle video cassettes (3), undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- School files, 1964-1993; RG0015 Series 4; 10.5 Linear feet
  This series contains annual reports, administrative files, by-laws, conferences, faculty reports and meetings, graduate assistants, committee records, work study programs, and dean's appointment books. The material covers the dates 1964-93.
  - School files, undated (Box 1)
  - Annual reports (faculty/SPIA), 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual reports (faculty/SPIA), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual reports, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty appointment letters, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty appointment -- full time, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty appointment, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty appointment letters (part-time), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faculty reports, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Faculty reports, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty reports, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Faculty reports, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Faculty reports, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Faculty reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Faculty reports, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Faculty reports, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Faculty reports, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Faculty recruitment, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Faculty recruitment, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Faculty recruitment, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Faculty evaluations by Dean Stout, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - School files, undated (Box 2)
  - Academic dishonesty, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Academic open house (annual) sponsored by admissions, Columbian College peer advisors, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Administrative, SPIA, 1966-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Administrative, SPIA, 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Administrative files, fire and safety, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Administrative - Intra.Dept. Promotion Recommendation SPIA/Admissions Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - SPIA/Admissions Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Advising: Transfer Students, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ALCOA Foundation, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ALCOA Foundation Grant/Library Support/SPIA, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American College in Paris and other schools/programs abroad, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Annual reports, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Annual student letter, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Appointments and promotions/SPIA, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Award S. Pinkney Tuck, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Book orders/library, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Budget -- Equal Opportunity Report, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Budget -- Equal Opportunity Report, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Budget -- memos on procedure, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - By Laws, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - By Laws Fac. List, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Calendar, 1972-1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 90 Degree Hour Candidates, SPIA, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Catalog copy, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Catalog copy, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Catalog copy, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Catalog copy, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Catalog copy, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Closed study applications, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Code Sheet Current, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - College of Gen. Studies (CCS), undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - College of Gen. Studies, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Columbian College, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Commencement, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Commencement, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Speaker Reception (James Robinson), 05/1977 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Committee/ SPIA Programs & Curriculum, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - School files, undated (Box 3)
  - Citadel Conference (Charleston, SC), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 38
  - US Military Academy Stud. Conference, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 39
  - US Naval Academy Foreign Affairs Conference, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 40
  - Student Conferences - 1 of 2 SCUSA & Naval Academy, USAFA, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 41
  - Student Conferences Contact 2 of 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 42
  - US Naval Academy - Foreign Affairs Conference (NAFAC), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 43
  - Consortium for International Studies Educ. & ISA Educ. Com., undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 44
  - Council of Academic Deans, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 45
  - Curriculum Matters, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 46
  - Dean's Council Committee - SPIA, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 47
  - Diplomat - in - Residence Re: Shirley Hendsch Double Major, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    formerly folder 48
  - ISSS - East Asian Lang. & Lit., 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    formerly folder 49
  - ISSS - East Asian Lang. & Lit., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    formerly folder 50
  - ISSS - East Asian Lang. & Lit., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    formerly folder 51
  - ISSS - East Asian Lang. & Lit., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    formerly folder 52
  - ISSS - East Asian Lang. & Lit., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    formerly folder 53
  - Educational Privacy Act, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    formerly folder 54
  - Enrollment in SPIA - BA & MA Prog., undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    formerly folder 55
  - Experimental Programs (Prof. Mondale), undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    formerly folder 56
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    formerly folder 57
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs Business, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    formerly folder 58
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 10/04/1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    formerly folder 59
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 12/06/1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    formerly folder 60
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    formerly folder 61
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 03/07/1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    formerly folder 62
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs (Reports), 03/07/1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    formerly folder 63
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 05/02/1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    formerly folder 64
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 05/02/1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    formerly folder 65
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 10/03/1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    formerly folder 66
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 12/1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    formerly folder 67
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 12/05/1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    formerly folder 68
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs Follow-up, 12/05/1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    formerly folder 69
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 01/08/1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    formerly folder 70
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 03/13/1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    formerly folder 71
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 03/13/1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    formerly folder 72
  - School files, undated (Box 4)
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 05/01/1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 73
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 05/1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 74
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 10/02/1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 75
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 03/05/1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 76
  - SPIA Faculty Mtgs, 01/08/1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 77
  - Faculty Mtg Minutes, 03/05/1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 78
  - Faculty Mtg Minutes, 05/07/1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 79
  - Faculty Mtg, 10/01/1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 80
  - SPIA Faculty Mtg, 10/1/1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 81
  - Faculty Mtg, 12/03/1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 82
  - Faculty Mtg, 03/03/1971-05/07/1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    formerly folder 83
  - Faculty Mtg, 05/05/1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    formerly folder 84
  - Faculty Mtg, 04/07/1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    formerly folder 85
  - Faculty Mtg, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    formerly folder 86
  - Faculty Mtg, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    formerly folder 87
  - SPlA/FAIP-Candidates - In Re: Academic Program, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    formerly folder 88
  - SPIA/FAIP Advisory Council Misc., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    formerly folder 89
  - Fellowship Information Centers National Fellowship Information, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    formerly folder 90
  - Finanical Aid/Student General Information Incoming Correspondence, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    formerly folder 91
  - Foreign Affairs Conference, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    formerly folder 92
  - SPIA/Foreign Affairs Intern Prog. (Institution & Administration), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    formerly folder 93
  - SPIA/Foreign Affairs Intern Prog., 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    formerly folder 94
  - SPIA/Grading Standards, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    formerly folder 95
  - German Society for Foreign Affairs: Its Research Institute, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    formerly folder 96
  - Graduate Student Reccuitment - SPIA, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    formerly folder 97
  - Graduate Admissions Office - SPIA, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    formerly folder 98
  - Graduate Assistants, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    formerly folder 99
  - Graduate Assistants, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    formerly folder 100
  - Graduate Assistants, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    formerly folder 101
  - Graduate Assistants, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    formerly folder 102
  - Graduate Assistants, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    formerly folder 103
  - Mtgs of the Graduate Stud. In SPIA, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    formerly folder 104
  - Handbook for GWU: Policies & Procedures, 07/19/1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    formerly folder 105
  - Hatchet Articles, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    formerly folder 106
  - Inquiries-General/SPIA, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    formerly folder 107
  - Inquiries General, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    formerly folder 108
  - Internships (Possible for Future), undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    formerly folder 109
  - International Communication Agency, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    formerly folder 110
  - International Students/General Information, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
    formerly folder 111
  - Joint Committee of Fac. & Students, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    formerly folder 112
  - Joint Committee of Fac. & Students, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
    formerly folder 113
  - School files, undated (Box 5)
  - Library/General, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 114
  - Memos - Misc. Incoming - Outgoing, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 115
  - Middle States Accreditation Self-Study, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 116
  - Orientation Coordinating Committee, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 117
  - Orientation Coordinating Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 118
  - Orientation Coordinating, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 119
  - Overseas Education Program, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 120
  - Parking Information, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 121
  - Ph.D. in Int'l Relations, 1972-1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 122
  - Ph.D. Thesis - Mrs. Coates, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 123
  - Political Science Dept. Curriculum Committee, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    formerly folder 124
  - Political Simulations, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    formerly folder 125
  - President James A. Robinson Commencement Speaker with Honors, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    formerly folder 126
  - Presidental Management Intern Program Info, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    formerly folder 127
  - Proposals/Miscellaneous (Public Affairs Proposal), undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    formerly folder 128
  - Proposal #1 Undergraduate Urban Affairs, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    formerly folder 129
  - Proposal #2 Undergraduate U.A. Programs, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    formerly folder 130
  - Proposed American Studies - Int'l Center at GWU, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    formerly folder 131
  - Proposed Intercultural Program with Georgetown University, 03/17/1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    formerly folder 132
  - Proposed "Law & Society" B.A. Program in SPIA, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    formerly folder 133
  - Proposed Legis. Studies Project (with former Mem. of Congress), undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    formerly folder 134
  - Proposed - Semester Abroad, College of Europe, 06/19/1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    formerly folder 135
  - Proposed Urban Affairs Program (Clias Marstella), undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    formerly folder 136
  - Recommendations - Letters of & Pertaining to, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    formerly folder 137
  - Registrar's Office/Memos, etc., undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    formerly folder 138
  - Report of the Subcommittee on Modified Semester, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    formerly folder 139
  - ROTC Courses, Credit for, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    formerly folder 140
  - Savings Bonds Campaign, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    formerly folder 141
  - Security (Correspondence/Memos,Misc. ), undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    formerly folder 142
  - Social Events - SPIA Sponsored, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    formerly folder 143
  - Civilian/Military Institute (Symposium ) SFAAC, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    formerly folder 144
  - SFAAC, SPIA Chairman: Daniel Hicena; Chairman: Howard Rosen; Chairman: C.D. Politis, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    formerly folder 145
  - SFAAC Minutes 09/1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    formerly folder 146
  - SFAAC (Projects) 1) Student Advisers 2) SCUSA 3) Newsletter, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    formerly folder 147
  - Student - Faculty - Alumni-Advisory Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    formerly folder 148
  - School files, undated (Box 6)
  - Student-Faculty-Alumni-Advisory Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 149
  - Special Lectures, Forums, Panels, Etc. - SPIA Sponsored, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 150
  - Student Inspection of File (Procedures, Background), 02/05/1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 151
  - Summer Sessions, Advisory Council to the Dean of, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 152
  - Telephone Info; TDK Systems Automated Call Processing System General, 05/1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 153
  - United Nations Association Congressional Internship, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 154
  - United Nations, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 155
  - United Way, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 156
  - United Way, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 157
  - United Way, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 158
  - United Way Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    formerly folder 159
  - United Way Campaign, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    formerly folder 160
  - U.G.F., 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    formerly folder 161
  - Urban Affairs at GW Prog., Personnel, Recruiting, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    formerly folder 162
  - Urban Affairs Student Committee, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    formerly folder 163
  - Work-Study Internship Material (Academic Year), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    formerly folder 164
  - Work-Study Internship Material (Academic Year), 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    formerly folder 165
  - Work Study & Internship Program State Dept. (Applicants; Meeting Info.; Recomm.), undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    formerly folder 166
  - Work Study Program - Dept. of State, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    formerly folder 167